Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Pause
Rud Iscandar.
Ghale Garmillan!
Ghale Iscandar!
Ghale Desler!
Ghale Phuzeron!
Operations Officer Mori Rescue Plan
Celebrate reaching the Large Magellanic with a
Magellan
Parfait!
Operations Officer Mor
Rescue
Episode 22
The Planet That We Head For
Among the distant stars
Can you hear the wandering souls?
In this galaxy, they can forever rest in peace
Requiem of separation
With this requiem
Sing Along!
Voices sing to praise
An unforgettable memory
And we’ll never forget your name
Farewell friend,
my sorrow
Will not run out
Someday in this sea of stars
Surely
Pray for the Earth!
The oath
Pray for the dream!
The ideal
Last forever!